http://www.mayakobagolfclassic.com/legal-statement/

November 30 – December 6, 2020El Camaleón Golf Club - Playa del Carmen, Quintana Roo, México
OHL Classic at MayakobaTournamentPolicy For 2020More than Just GolfSchedule of EventsProfessional ParticipantsTee TimesTelevision TimesTournament HistoryResults & EarningsThe CourseCharityGolf PARa TodosTournament StaffContact UsMediaLatest NewsFrom the Media CenterPhoto GalleriesVideosMedia Credential ApplicationMedia Q & ALogosImage & Video DownloadsEmail NewsletterAmbassadorsAmbassador CommitteesAmbassador Q&AExecutive Volunteer CouncilAlliancesFounding PartnersCorporate PartnersBranding & AdvertisingPro-Am ExperienceHospitality & EntertainmentCorporate Alliance OpportunitiesMayakobaBanyan Tree MayakobaFairmont MayakobaRosewood MayakobaAndaz MayakobaEl Camaleón Golf ClubJim McLean Golf SchoolMayakoba™ ResidencesCiudad MayakobaRLH PropertiesRiviera MayaTequila PatrónUNIFINEspañol
Legal Statement
Privacy Policy
Golf de Mayakoba, S.A. de C.V. located in Carretera Federal km 298 Chetumal-Puerto Juárez, Playa del Carmen, Quintana Roo, México, Mayakoba, its shareholders, representatives, partners, operators and/or subsidiaries and related companies (Mayakoba) agree to comply with the current legislation in in regards to the automated data processing systems and in particular with the Mexican Federal Law on the Protection of Personal Data Held by Private Parties, according to the following privacy notice:.
The information obtained through this site is only used for the purposes intended and stipulated at the time of collection. This information is not shared with other entities for purposes other than those provided or shared with third parties unless otherwise stated when requested. If such information can be shared with any entity, the authorization of the visitor will be sought in advance.
Mayakoba makes every effort to avoid excessive or irrelevant collection of data. If a visitor believes the site has collected excessive information, we encourage you to contact us and express your concerns info@mayakobagolfclassic.com. Excluding the newsletter mailing list, where visitors openly choose to receive specific materials, Mayakoba will not use the personal information collected on our websites to send unsolicited marketing campaigns. If you want to limit the use or disclosure of your personal information, exercise your right to access, correct and cancel your personal data as well as to oppose to the usage of your data or revoke the consent that was given to us, you may contact us through the following service channels: via telephone at 984 873 4900 or via e-mail at info@mayakobagolfclassic.com, where you will be informed of the procedures to exercise the rights set forth herein.
Golf de Mayakoba,
S.A. de C.V. has implemented technology services and security standards generally accepted to prevent the lost, misuse, alteration and destroyed personal information. Mayakoba reserves the right to modify or amend this privacy notice at any time. In order to keep stakeholders informed, Mayakoba will notify users of any changes made to the privacy notice, clearly indicating the changes in our home page for at least two weeks: http://mayakobagolfclassic.com.
Home
TournamentPolicy For 2020More than Just GolfSchedule of EventsProfessional ParticipantsTee TimesTelevision TimesTournament HistoryResults & EarningsThe CourseCharityGolf PARa TodosTournament StaffContact UsMediaLatest NewsFrom the Media CenterPhoto GalleriesVideosMedia Credential ApplicationMedia Q & ALogosImage & Video DownloadsEmail NewsletterAmbassadorsAmbassador CommitteesAmbassador Q&AExecutive Volunteer CouncilAlliancesFounding PartnersCorporate PartnersBranding & AdvertisingPro-Am ExperienceHospitality & EntertainmentCorporate Alliance OpportunitiesMayakobaBanyan Tree MayakobaFairmont MayakobaRosewood MayakobaAndaz MayakobaEl Camaleón Golf ClubJim McLean Golf SchoolMayakoba™ ResidencesCiudad MayakobaRLH PropertiesRiviera MayaTequila PatrónUNIFINSocial MediaTwitterFacebookInstagram Español
© 2013-Present, Mayakoba Golf Classic. All Rights Reserved.    Legal Statement
